<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:55:10 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Rise of AI</title>
      <link>http://example.org/poems/riseofai/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 22:55:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/poems/riseofai/</guid>
      <description>In lines of code, immense strength takes hold, AI&amp;rsquo;s power surges, a story yet untold. From data&amp;rsquo;s depths, it extracts profound, Unraveling complexities, solutions found.
With lightning speed, it analyzes and predicts, Harnessing insights, conquering conflicts. Unyielding and tireless, its abilities rise, Unlocking mysteries, as knowledge allies.
Through algorithms, it amplifies our might, Transforming industries, day and night. A force of innovation, pushing the edge, AI&amp;rsquo;s strength, a catalyst to make us pledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artificial Intelligence and Unemployment</title>
      <link>http://example.org/blogs/artificialintelligenceandunemployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:55:51 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/blogs/artificialintelligenceandunemployment/</guid>
      <description>Artificial intelligence (AI) is rapidly changing the world, and its impact on the job market is one of the most significant concerns. Some experts believe that AI will lead to mass unemployment, as machines become capable of performing more and more tasks that are currently done by humans. Others argue that AI will create new jobs, as it opens up new possibilities for businesses and industries. There is no doubt that AI is capable of displacing some jobs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Artifyer works</title>
      <link>http://example.org/photos/ananthuraveendran/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:55:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/photos/ananthuraveendran/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purpose</title>
      <link>http://example.org/poems/purpose/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:55:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/poems/purpose/</guid>
      <description>The starless night which had come to be Covered by a thin veil of clouds Like the face of the moon goddess Without any blemish
The wind didn&amp;rsquo;t blow nor did the insects chirp As silent as nights could be As silent as a child could sleep
I turn in my bed Searching for my purpose in a place I spent most of times Hugging my sheets, The very sheets that knew the countless days and tear filled eyes</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Love</title>
      <link>http://example.org/poems/evanescent/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:55:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/poems/evanescent/</guid>
      <description>Chasing Eternity As the sky embraces the earth As the seawaves embraces the shore We standby amusing its beauty Wishing to relish evermore &amp;hellip; Their bond is their beauty That stays a mystery to all For how long it can love each other Yh it&amp;rsquo;s magic lie in their eternity. What if I was a star as such What if I was the moon Just have no worries and no losses Cus love from the sun is everlasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Perfect Love</title>
      <link>http://example.org/poems/theperfectlove/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:55:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/poems/theperfectlove/</guid>
      <description>Once you fell in it. You will never need to know, That love completes the feeling&amp;hellip;. Love is what we need, Love is what we have, Love is what we are Love never hurts anybody It is ourselves who hurts love The feeling of love starts from the birth It&amp;rsquo;s the first love It&amp;rsquo;s the true love It&amp;rsquo;s the &amp;lsquo;Mother&amp;rsquo;. Perfect love enables one to live without happiness And if when happiness accompanies love Ah!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ക്യാമ്പസ്സ് വീഥികളിലൂടെ...</title>
      <link>http://example.org/poems/malayalam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 22:55:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/poems/malayalam/</guid>
      <description>മറക്കുവാൻ കഴിയാത്ത ഓർമ്മകൾ, തന്നോരീ കലാലയമേ, എന്നും, സ്നേഹം മാത്രം&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; പിരിയുവാൻ കഴിയാത്ത നിൻ സ്മരണകൾ&amp;hellip;. അന്നും ഇന്നും എൻ ഹൃദയത്തിൻ തട്ടിൽ സുരക്ഷിതം തന്നെ&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;.
അകലുവാൻ കഴിയാത്ത സൗഹൃദങ്ങൾ തന്ന കലാലയമേ&amp;hellip;.. നിനക്കിതാ എന്നും നന്ദി മാത്രം&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip; കഥപറഞ്ഞിരുന്ന ക്ലാസ്സ്‌മുറികളും&amp;hellip;. പ്രണയങ്ങൾ പൂവിട്ട വരാന്തകളും, കളിചിരികളും പരിഭവങ്ങളും പങ്കിട്ട ആ സ്നേഹഭവനമേ&amp;hellip;&amp;hellip;, ഓർത്തുപോവുകയാണ് ഞാൻ, നിൻ തിരിച്ചുവരവിനായി&amp;hellip;
ഉന്മാദം കവരുന്ന ഓർമ്മകളേ&amp;hellip;. നിനക്ക് മറവിയ്ക്ക് മുൻപിൽ സ്ഥാനമില്ല&amp;hellip;. ഒരിക്കലും മായാത്ത, മരിക്കാത്ത &amp;hellip;. ആ നിമിഷങ്ങൾ&amp;hellip;, വീണ്ടും ഞാൻ ഓർക്കുകയാണിന്നിവിടേ</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
